Preliminary Guide to the Africa News Service (Durham, N.C.) Leroy T. Walker Africa News Service Archive, 1952-1998 and undated (bulk 1952-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- World (Box 286)
  - Groups (Box 305)
    - World Council of Churches (Box 306)
      - thru 1973, 1974-93, (3 folders) (Box 306)
      - African Programs thru 1972, 1973-, (6 folders) (Box 306)
      - "Churches Responding to Racism in the 1980's " (Box 306)
      - Justice Et Service (Box 306)
    - World Evangelical Fellowship (Box 306)
    - World Federation of Democratic Youth (Box 306)
    - World Festival of Youth and Students (Box 306)
    - World Methodist Council (Box 306)
    - World Peace Council (Box 306)
    - World Peace Through Law (Box 306)
    - World Student Christian Federation, thru 1983, 1984-, (2 folders) (Box 306)
    - World University Service (Box 306)
    - World Wildlife Fund (Box 306)
  - Health, thru 1982; 1983-86 (Box 306)
  - Health (Box 307)
    - 1987-93, (3 folders) (Box 307)
    - AIDS, 1985-94, (6 folders) (Box 307)
    - Depo Provera (Box 307)
    - Malaria (Box 307)
  - Labor (Box 307)
  - Labor: Relations with Southern Africa, 1976-80, (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Language (Box 307)
  - Legal Systems (Box 307)
  - Media, 1974-79 (Box 307)
  - Media (Box 308)
    - 1980-94, (2 folders) (Box 308)
    - World Administrative Radio Conference (WARC) (Box 308)
  - Military (Box 308)
    - thru 1982, 1997, (2 folders) (Box 308)
    - Chemical/Biological Weapons (Box 308)
    - Disarmament (Box 308)
    - Expenditures (Box 308)
    - Indian Ocean, thru 1977, 1978-, (2 folders) (Box 308)
    - Intelligence (Box 308)
    - Mercenaries (Box 308)
    - NATO, pre 1975, 1975-85, (3 folders) (Box 308)
      - Southern Africa, thru 1975, 1976-1982, (4 folders) (Box 308)
    - Nuclear (Box 309)
    - Nuclear: Non-Proliferation, thru 1977, 1978-, (4 folders) (Box 309)
  - Politics (Box 309)
    - Arab League (Box 309)
    - Commonwealth (Box 309)
      - thru 1979, 1979-, (4 folders) (Box 309)
      - Relations with South Africa Eminent Persons Group (Box 309)
    - Communism (Box 309)
    - Human Rights (Box 309)
      - thru 1989, 1989-, (3 folders) (Box 309)
      - Indigenous People (ethnic conflict) (Box 309)
      - PIOOM (Box 309)
    - Ideologies and Philosophizing (Box 309)
    - Industrialized Countries (Box 309)
    - Nobel Peace Prize (Box 309)
    - Non-Aligned Conferences (Box 309)
    - Non-Aligned Movement, thru 1978, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 309)
    - Non-Aligned Movement, 1980-95, (2 folders) (Box 310)
    - Outerspace (Box 310)
    - Right Wing (Box 310)
    - Terrorism, thru 1985, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 310)
  - Religions (Box 310)
    - Catholicism (Box 310)
    - Christianity - Protestantism (Box 310)
    - General (Box 310)
    - Islam (Box 310)
      - thru 1992, 1993-97, (2 folders) (Box 310)
      - Salmon Rushdie Affair (Box 310)
  - Refugees, 1976-1997, (4 folders) (Box 310)
  - Sports, thru 1983, 1984-88, (3 folders) (Box 310)
  - Third World: Neocolonialism (Box 310)
  - Women: thru 1984, 1985-89, (2 folders) (Box 310)
- World: United Nations (Box 310)
  - Africa (Box 311)
  - Africa: Economic Commission for Africa (Box 311)
  - Aid and Development (Box 311)
  - Angola Peace Talks, 1992-1993, (3 folders) (Box 311)
  - Decolonization (Box 311)
  - Disarmament Conference (Box 311)
  - FAO (Food & Agriculture Organization) (Box 311)
  - General, thru 1978, 1979-89, (6 folders) (Box 311)
  - General 1989-1996 (Box 312)
  - General Assembly (Box 312)
    - 29th-35th & 38th Sessions, (8 folders) (Box 312)
    - 1981-1994 (Box 312)
  - General Information (Box 312)
  - Habitat Conference (Box 312)
  - Human Rights Commission (Box 312)
  - International Fund for Agricultural Development (IFAD) (Box 312)
  - ILO (Box 312)
  - ILO: Press Releases and Newsletters (Box 312)
  - International Literacy Year (Box 312)
  - ITU (International Telecommunications Union) (Box 312)
  - International Year of the Child (Box 312)
  - IYDP (International Year of the Disabled) (Box 312)
  - Liberia (Box 312)
  - Mozambique (Box 312)
  - Namibia (Box 312)
  - Quaker UN Office (Box 312)
  - UN Peacekeeping Forces, thru 1992, 1993-94, (2 folders) (Box 312)
  - Racial Discrimination (Box 312)
  - Security Council (Box 313)
  - Security Council: Debate on Armed Military Aggression by U.S. vs. Libya (Box 313)
  - Secretary General (Box 313)
  - Somalia, 1992-94, (5 folders) (Box 313)
  - Rels. South Africa, 1975-80, (4 folders) (Box 313)
  - Rels. South Africa, 1981-94, (4 folders) (Box 314)
  - Rels. Southern Africa, thru 1976, 1977-86, (4 folders) (Box 314)
  - UNCTAD (see also World Economy UNCTAD) (Box 314)
  - UNDTCD (Box 314)
  - UNDRO (UN Disaster Relief Office) (Box 314)
  - UNEP and Environment General, thru 1990 (Box 314)
  - UNEP/UNCED (Environment) 1991-92 (Box 314)
  - UNEP 1993 (Box 314)
  - UNICEF (Box 314)
  - UNICEF: News Features/Press Summaries (Box 314)
  - UNDP (Box 314)
  - UNIDO (Box 315)
  - UNESCO, thru 1983, 1984-93, (2 folders) (Box 315)
  - UNCHR (Box 315)
  - UN University (Box 315)
  - Western Sahara (Box 315)
  - Women (Box 315)
  - Women: Decade for Women (Box 315)
    - Pre-Nairobi Meeting Clips (Box 315)
    - Nairobi Clips (Box 315)
    - Forum, 1985 (Box 315)
  - World Summit for Children (Box 316)
    - 1990 (Box 316)
    - Official Statements (Box 316)
    - Reference (Box 316)
  - WHO (World Health Organization) (Box 316)
  - Zimbabwe (Box 316)
- World: Asia (Box 316)
  - Asia (Box 316)
    - Economy-Oil (Box 316)
    - General (Box 316)
  - Bangladesh (Box 316)
  - Cambodia (Box 316)
  - China (People's Republic) (Box 316)
    - Foreign Relations, 1979-1982, (2 folders) (Box 316)
    - Relations with Africa, thru 1986, (5 folders) (Box 316)
    - African Students in 1989 China Riots (Box 316)
    - General (Box 316)
    - Groups: The Afro-Asian Journalist (Box 316)
  - Cyprus (Box 316)
  - East Timor, (4 folders) (Box 316)
  - Hong Kong (Box 316)
  - India (Box 316)
  - Indonesia (Box 316)
  - Japan (Box 317)
    - Economy (Box 317)
    - Economy: Oil (Box 317)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 317)
      - Africa (Box 317)
      - South Africa - Nuclear (Box 317)
      - Southern Africa (Box 317)
    - General (Box 317)
    - Groups (Box 317)
      - AMPO (Box 317)
      - Worker's Communist Committee (Box 317)
  - Macao (Box 317)
  - Malaysia (Box 317)
  - New Caledonia (Box 317)
  - New Hebrides (Box 317)
  - North Korea (Box 317)
  - Pakistan (Box 317)
  - Papua-New Guinea (Box 317)
  - Philippines (Box 317)
  - Singapore (Box 317)
  - South Korea (Box 317)
  - Sri Lanka (Box 317)
  - Taiwan (Box 317)
  - Thailand (Box 317)
  - U.S. Samoa (Box 317)
  - Vietnam (Box 317)
- World: Australia (Box 317)
  - Foreign Relations (Box 317)
  - Foreign Relations - Africa (Box 317)
    - General (Box 317)
    - Groups (Box 317)
    - Association for Internal Cooperation and Disarmament (Box 317)
    - Australian Union of Students (Committee for Liberation of Timor-Dili) (Box 317)
    - CARE (Campaign vs. Racial Exploitation) (Box 317)
    - Southern Africa Liberation Centre (Box 317)
- World: Canada (Box 317)
  - Economy (Box 317)
  - Foreign Relations (Box 317)
    - Africa (Box 317)
    - Southern Africa (Box 317)
    - Southern Africa, 1972-1982, (7 folders) (Box 318)
  - General (Box 318)
  - African Groups (Box 318)
    - African Clarion (Box 318)
    - Afro-Asian-Latin American Peoples' Solidarity Committee (Third World Forum) (Box 318)
    - ANC (Box 318)
    - ARSO (Africa Relief Services Committee) (Box 318)
    - Canadian Association of African Students (Box 318)
    - Contrast (Box 318)
    - CUSO (Box 318)
    - Free Southern Africa Committee (FSAC) (Box 318)
    - Liberation Support Movement (Box 318)
    - Southern Africa Information Group (Box 318)
    - TCLPAC (Box 318)
    - TCLSAC, 1975-1984, (5 folders) (Box 318)
  - Groups (Box 318)
    - AMEX (Americans Exiled in Canada) (Box 318)
    - Association Quebec--Palestine (Fedayin) (Box 318)
    - Churches (The United Church of Canada) (Box 318)
    - Canada Information Sharing Service (CISS) (Box 318)
    - Development and Peace (Box 318)
    - Development Education Center (Box 318)
    - GATT Fly (Box 318)
    - OXFAM (Box 318)
    - Vietnamese Patriots in Canada (Box 318)
    - YWCA of Canada (Box 318)
  - Media (Box 318)
- World: New Zealand (Box 318)
  - Foreign Relations - Africa (Box 319)
  - Groups: CARE (Citizens' Association for Racial Equality, Inc.) (Box 319)
  - Relations with Africa, 1975-86, (2 folders) (Box 319)
- World: Europe (Box 319)
  - Europe (Box 319)
    - Economy, thru 1984, (3 folders) (Box 319)
    - Banking (Box 319)
    - E.E.C. (Box 319)
    - Foreign Workers, (2 folders) (Box 319)
    - Oil (Box 319)
  - Foreign Relations: Africa (Box 319)
  - Economy, thru 1984, (2 folders) (Box 319)
  - Politics, thru 1985, (2 folders) (Box 319)
  - Portugal and Portuguese Colonialism (Box 319)
  - Southern Africa, thru 1978 (Box 319)
  - Groups (Box 319)
    - Africa (Box 319)
      - Free the Pretoria 12 (Box 319)
      - Free Southern Africa Committee (Box 319)
      - AGAPE (Box 320)
      - Association of West European Parlimentarians for Action Against Apartheid (Box 320)
      - Development and Peace (Box 320)
      - Ecumenical Committee for Church & Society (Box 320)
  - Media - Tanjug (Box 320)
  - Politics (Box 320)
  - Albania (Box 320)
  - Austria (Box 320)
  - Bavaria (Box 320)
  - Belgium (Box 320)
  - Bulgaria (Box 320)
  - Czechoslovakia (Box 320)
  - Denmark (Box 320)
  - Finland (Box 320)
  - France (Box 320)
    - Bibliography (Box 320)
    - Economy (Box 320)
    - Foreign Relations, (2 folders) (Box 320)
    - Foreign Relations: Africa (Box 320)
      - thru 1981, (9 folders) (Box 320)
      - 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 321)
      - Economy (Box 321)
      - Military (Box 321)
      - Sports (Box 321)
      - Students (Box 321)
    - Foreign Relations: North Africa, thru 1983, (4 folders) (Box 321)
    - Foreign Relations: South Africa (Box 321)
      - thru 1987, (5 folders) (Box 321)
      - Nuclear (Box 321)
  - France (Box 321)
    - Foreign Relations: Southern Africa (Box 321)
    - Groups (Box 321)
      - IEE (Institute International D'Etudes Sur L'Education) (Box 321)
      - Africa: Comite Francais Contre L'Apartheid (Box 321)
    - Media (Box 321)
    - Military (Box 321)
    - Politics (Box 321)
    - Religion (Box 321)
  - Germany (Democratic Republic), thru 1980, (2 folders) (Box 321)
    - Germany (Democratic Republic) (Box 322)
      - 1981-1988 (Box 322)
    - Groups: Africa (Box 322)
      - Afrika Heute III Welt (Box 322)
      - Deutsches Komite For Angola (Box 322)
      - ISSA (Informationsdienst Sudliches Africa) (Box 322)
  - Germany (Federal Republic) (Box 322)
    - General (Box 322)
    - Foreign Relations: South Africa, Nuclear (Box 322)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 322)
  - Greece (Box 322)
  - Hungary (Box 322)
    - General (Box 322)
    - Groups: World Youth (Box 322)
  - Ireland (Box 322)
    - General (Box 322)
    - Groups: IR Movement (Box 322)
  - Italy (Box 322)
    - General (Box 322)
    - Groups: Liberazione e Sviluppo (Box 322)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 322)
  - Liechtenstein (Box 322)
  - Malta (Box 322)
    - Netherlands (Box 322)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 322)
    - Foreign Relations: Africa (Box 322)
    - Foreign Relations: South Africa, Nuclear (Box 322)
    - General (Box 322)
    - Groups: Africa (Box 322)
      - Angola Comite (Box 322)
      - Azania Komitee (Box 322)
      - Comite Zuid Afrika (Box 322)
      - HP (Dossier Zuikelijk--Afrika) (Box 322)
      - Kairos (Box 322)
    - Religion (Box 322)
  - Norway (Box 323)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 323)
  - Poland (Box 323)
  - Portugal (Box 323)
    - Bibliography (Box 323)
      - Economy, thru 1979, (2 folders) (Box 323)
    - General, thru 1984, (6 folders) (Box 323)
    - Groups: Africa, ASSOCIACO Portugal Angola (Box 323)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 323)
      - thru 1983, (3 folders) (Box 323)
      - Refugees (Box 323)
    - NATO (Box 323)
    - Women (Box 323)
  - Romania (Box 323)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 323)
  - Scandinavia (Box 323)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 323)
  - Spain (Box 323)
    - General (Box 323)
  - Sweden (Box 323)
    - General (Box 323)
    - Groups: Africa, International Defence and Aid Fund for South Africa (Box 323)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 323)
  - Switzerland (Box 323)
    - General (Box 323)
      - Groups: Africa (Box 323)
      - Comite Sudliehes Africa (Committee Southern Africa) (Box 323)
      - Mouvement Anti-Apartheid de Suisse (Box 323)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 323)
    - United Kingdom (Box 324)
      - Bibliography (Box 324)
    - Economy, 1975-1983, (3 folders) (Box 324)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 324)
      - Africa (Box 324)
        - thru 1985, (4 folders) (Box 324)
        - Sports (Box 324)
      - Libya, 1984 (Box 324)
      - Portugal and Portuguese Colonialism (Box 324)
      - Rhodesia, thru 1979, (6 folders) (Box 324)
      - South Africa (Box 324)
        - thru 1975, (2 folders) (Box 324)
          - 1976-1990, (11 folders) (Box 325)
          - Economy, thru 1985, (3 folders) (Box 325)
          - Military, thru 1976, (2 folders) (Box 326)
          - Nuclear (Box 326)
        - Southern Africa, thru 1980 (Box 326)
        - Zimbabwe (Box 326)
  - Groups (Box 326)
    - Africa (Box 326)
      - Miscellaneous (includes numerous groups) (Box 326)
      - Angola Solidarity Committee (Box 326)
      - Anti-Apartheid Movement (Box 326)
      - Azania (Box 326)
      - Committee for Freedom in Mozambique, Angola, and Guinea, (2 folders) (Box 326)
      - End Loans to Southern Africa (ELISA) (Box 326)
      - International African Institute (Box 326)
      - International Defense Aid (Box 326)
      - Liberation Struggle (Box 326)
      - Namibia Research Project (Box 326)
      - Study Project on International Investments in South Africa (Box 326)
    - All Faiths for One Race (AFFOR) (Box 326)
    - Anti-Slavery Society (Box 326)
    - British Council of Churches (Box 326)
    - Center for International Briefing (Box 326)
    - Europe-Third World Research Center (Box 326)
    - Foreign Affairs Research Institute (Box 326)
    - Institute for the Study of Conflict (Box 326)
    - Institute of Development Studies (Box 326)
    - Minority Rights Group (Box 326)
    - Namibia Support Committee (Box 326)
    - Organizations and Constituency (Box 326)
    - OXFAM--OXFAM International (Box 326)
    - Returned Volunteers Action Organization (Box 326)
    - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 326)
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs (Box 326)
    - Youth Organizations of Southern Africa (Box 326)
    - United Kingdom (Box 327)
      - Media (Box 327)
      - Africa Coverage, Opinion (Box 327)
      - BBC (Box 327)
      - Economist (Box 327)
      - Financial Times (Box 327)
      - Gemini News Service (Box 327)
      - General (Box 327)
      - Guardian (Box 327)
      - New Internationalist (Box 327)
      - Observer (Box 327)
      - Reuters (Box 327)
      - Times (Box 327)
      - Third World Quarterly (Box 327)
    - Military (Box 327)
    - Politics (Box 327)
    - Race Relations (Box 327)
  - U.S.S.R. (Box 327)
    - Economy (Box 327)
    - Economy, Oil (Box 327)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 327)
      - thru 1983, (3 folders) (Box 327)
      - Africa, thru 1986, (7 folders) (Box 327)
      - General, thru 1979, (2 folders) (Box 328)
      - Military (Box 328)
    - Yugoslavia (Box 328)
      - General (Box 328)
      - Relations with Africa (Box 328)
- World: Latin America (Box 328)
  - Latin America (Box 328)
    - Economy (Box 328)
      - Oil (Box 328)
    - General (Box 328)
    - Relations With Africa (Box 328)
  - Antigua (Box 328)
  - Argentina (Box 328)
  - Bahamas (Box 328)
  - Barbados (Box 328)
  - Belize (Box 328)
  - Bermuda (Box 328)
  - Bolivia (Box 328)
  - Brazil (Box 328)
    - Economy, Oil (Box 328)
    - General (Box 328)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 328)
    - Relations with Southern Africa (Box 328)
  - Caribbean (Box 328)
  - Chile, thru 1988, (2 folders) (Box 328)
  - Columbia (Box 328)
    - General (Box 328)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 328)
  - Costa Rica (Box 328)
  - Cuba (Box 329)
    - General, thru 1988, (3 folders) (Box 329)
    - Relations with (Box 329)
      - Africa, thru 1985, (7 folders) (Box 329)
      - Angola, 1976-1985, (5 folders) (Box 329)
      - Groups - OCLAE (Box 329)
    - Dominica (Box 329)
    - Dominican Republic, (2 folders) (Box 329)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 330)
  - Ecuador (Box 330)
  - El Salvador, 1979-1982, (4 folders) (Box 330)
  - Grenada (Box 330)
  - Guatemala (Box 330)
  - Guyana (Box 330)
  - Haiti (Box 330)
  - Honduras (Box 330)
  - Jamaica (Box 330)
  - Martinique (Box 330)
  - Mexico (Box 330)
    - Economy - Oil (Box 330)
    - General (Box 330)
  - Nicaragua (Box 330)
  - Panama (Box 330)
  - Paraguay (Box 330)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 330)
  - Peru (Box 330)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 330)
  - St. Lucia (Box 330)
  - Surinam (Box 330)
  - Trinidad (Box 330)
  - Uruguay, (2 folders) (Box 330)
  - Venezuela (Box 330)
    - Economy - Oil (Box 330)
    - General (Box 330)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 330)
  - Virgin Islands (Box 330)
- World: Middle East (Box 330)
  - Abu Dhabi (Box 331)
  - Afghanistan, thru 1988, (2 folders) (Box 331)
  - Bahrain (Box 331)
  - Brunei (Box 331)
  - Dhufar (Box 331)
  - Iran (Box 331)
    - Economy (Box 331)
      - thru 1982, (3 folders) (Box 331)
      - Oil (Box 331)
    - Military & Foreign Policy, thru 1984, (2 folders) (Box 331)
    - Politics, thru 1982, (3 folders) (Box 331)
    - Relations with Africa (Box 331)
    - Relations with South Africa, thru 1982, (3 folders) (Box 331)
  - Iraq (Box 331)
  - Israel (Box 331)
    - General (Box 331)
    - Foreign Relations, thru 1986, (4 folders) (Box 331)
    - Relations with Africa, thru 1986, (5 folders) (Box 331)
    - Relations with Southern Africa, thru 1984, (6 folders) (Box 332)
  - Jordan (Box 332)
  - Kuwait (Box 332)
  - Lebanon (Box 332)
  - Middle East (Box 332)
    - Bibliography (Box 332)
    - Economy, Oil (Box 332)
    - General, thru 1983, (2 folders) (Box 332)
    - Islam (Box 332)
    - Palestine Liberation Organization, thru 1989, (2 folders) (Box 332)
    - Palestine Refugees (Box 332)
  - North Yemen (Box 332)
  - Oman (Box 332)
  - Qatar (Box 332)
  - Saudi Arabia (Box 332)
  - South Yemen (Box 332)
  - Syria (Box 332)
  - Turkey (Box 332)
  - United Arab Emirates (Box 332)
- Persons (Box 332)
  Files in this series are about individuals including politicians, journalists, artists, business people, and military and movement leaders. Many have a specific African connection although some may not. A few of the names found here are Muhummad Ali, Steve Biko, Shirley Temple Black, Miriam Makeba, Ronald Reagan, and Walter Sisulu. Preceding the alphabetical listing of individuals' names is a folder for each letter of the alphabet that contains materials on several people. This file was maintained when there was only one or two articles about a person and did not yet warrant starting a separate folder.
  - "A" (Box 333)
    - Abrams, Elliot (Box 333)
    - Aaron, David L. (Box 333)
    - Abourezk, James (Box 333)
    - Adelman, Kenneth (Box 333)
    - Achebe, Chinua (Box 333)
    - Adedeji, Adebayo (Box 333)
    - Agee, Phil (Box 333)
    - Agee, William (Box 333)
    - Alexander, Clifford (Box 333)
    - Ali, Mohammed (Box 333)
    - Allen, Richard V. (Box 333)
    - Amin, Idi (Box 333)
    - Anderson, Bruce (Box 333)
    - Anderson, Jack (Box 333)
    - Anderson, John B. (Box 333)
    - Andrews, Ike (Box 333)
    - Angelou, Maya (Box 333)
    - Ardrey, Robert (Box 333)
    - Ashe, Arthur (Box 333)
    - Atwood, J. Brian (Box 333)
    - Auchincloss family (Box 333)
    - Axelson, Kenneth S. (Box 333)
  - "B" (Box 333)
    - Ba, Hampate (Box 333)
    - Bagley, Smith (Box 333)
    - Bailey, Steven K. (Box 333)
    - Baler, James III (Box 333)
    - Baldrige, Malcolm (Box 333)
    - Ball, George (Box 333)
    - Baraka, Amiri (Box 333)
    - Barber, James David (Box 333)
    - Barnard, Christian (Box 333)
    - Barnet, Richard J. (Box 333)
    - Barry, Marion (Box 333)
    - Bass family (Box 333)
    - Batten, William M. (Box 333)
    - Bauman, Robert E. (Box 333)
    - Beckman, David (Box 333)
    - Belafonte, Harry (Box 333)
    - Belk, John (Box 333)
    - Bell, Griffin B. (Box 333)
    - Bella, Ahmed Ben (Box 333)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd (Box 333)
    - Bergsten, C. Fred (Box 333)
    - Best, Kenneth (Box 333)
    - Biko, Steve (Box 333)
    - Bernhard, Prine (of Netherlands) (Box 333)
    - Black, Shirley Temple (Box 333)
    - Biehl, Amy Elizabeth (Box 333)
    - Blaustein, Albert (Box 333)
    - Block, John Rusling (Box 333)
    - Bloom, Anthony (Box 333)
    - Blumenthal, W. Michael (Box 333)
    - Boesak, Allen (Box 333)
    - Bol, Manute (Box 333)
    - Boggs, Thomas (Box 333)
    - Bond, Julian (Box 333)
    - Bonker, Don (Box 333)
    - Boothby, Neil (Box 333)
    - de Borchgrave, Arnaud (Box 333)
    - Botha, Pieter W. (Box 333)
    - Boutros-Ghali, Boutros (Box 333)
    - Bowe, Riddick (Box 333)
    - Bowles, Chester (Box 333)
    - Braden, Spruille (Box 333)
    - Brady, Nicholas (Box 333)
    - Brewster, Kingman (Box 333)
    - Breytenbach, Breyten (Box 333)
    - Brock, William E. (Box 333)
    - Bronfman, Edward and Charles (Box 333)
    - Brown, Edmund G., Jr. (Box 334)
    - Brown, Harold (Box 334)
    - Brown, Jerry (Box 334)
    - Brown, Robert J. (Box 334)
    - Brown, Ronald (Box 334)
    - Brown, Sam (Box 334)
    - Bruce, David K. E. (Box 334)
    - Brutus, Dennis (Box 334)
    - Buchanan, Patrick (Box 334)
    - Buchwald, Art (Box 334)
    - Buckley, James L. (Box 334)
    - Budd, Zola (Box 334)
    - Buckley, William F. (Box 334)
    - Bundy, McGeorge (Box 334)
    - Bunker, Ellsworth (Box 334)
    - Burchett, Wilfred (Box 334)
    - Burden family (Box 334)
    - Burns, Arthur (Box 334)
    - Bush, George (Box 334)
    - Butcher, Jake (Box 334)
    - Buthelezi, Mangosuthu Gatsha (Box 334)
    - Byrd, Robert (Box 334)
  - "C" (Box 334)
    - Cabral, Amilcar (Box 334)
    - Caputo, Philip (Box 334)
    - Carbaugh, John (Box 334)
    - Carlucci, Frank (Box 334)
    - Carmichael, Stokely (Box 334)
    - Carrington, (Lord) Peter A.R. (Box 334)
    - Carter, Gwendolen (Box 334)
    - Carter, Hodding (Box 334)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 334)
    - Carter, W. Beverly (Box 334)
    - Casey, William J. (Box 334)
    - Chihana, Chakufwa (Box 334)
    - Chatwin, Bruce (Box 334)
    - Chebeya, Floribert Bahizire (Box 334)
    - Cherne, Leo (Box 334)
    - Chikerema, James (Box 334)
    - Childs, Marquis (Box 334)
    - Chiluba, Frederick J.T. (Box 334)
    - Chisholm, Shirley (Box 334)
    - Christopher, Warren M. (Box 334)
    - Church, Frank (Box 334)
    - Clark, Clifford (Box 334)
    - Clark, Ramsey (Box 334)
    - Clark, Richard (Box 334)
    - Clark, William P. (Box 334)
    - Clausen, A.W. (Box 334)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box 334)
    - Cobb, Charles E. (Box 334)
    - Coetzee, J. M. (Box 334)
    - Cohen, Herman J. (Box 334)
    - Cohn, Roy (Box 334)
    - Cole, Johnnetta (Box 334)
    - Coleman, William T., Jr. (Box 334)
    - Colby, William (Box 334)
    - Commoner, Barry (Box 334)
    - Conant, James B. (Box 334)
    - Connally, John B. (Box 334)
    - Cosby, Bill (Box 334)
    - Cowan, Louis (Box 334)
    - Crane, Kent B. (Box 334)
    - Crane, Philip M. (Box 334)
    - Crocker, Chester A. (Box 334)
    - Crichton, Michael (Box 334)
    - Crowe, Philip K. (Box 334)
    - Culver, John (Box 334)
    - Cuneo, Ernest (Box 334)
    - Cunningham, Mary (Box 334)
  - "D" (Box 335)
    - Davidson, Basil (Box 335)
    - Davis, Chuck (Box 335)
    - Davis, John W. (Box 335)